You're really quite amazing.
You're the attendant to the demon
king and his daughter, Lady Doux.
I'm very proud to say that we went
to demon school together, Jahi.
There's nothing to be proud of!
I can't get Lady Doux
to pass a single trial,
and no matter how much I teach her,
she's not turning more demon-like at all!
Seriously, Lady Doux... will you
ever become a full-fledged demon?
I'm just... a totally useless attendant!
It must be rough working for the royals.
I wish she'd knock it off
with the drunk crying though.
One more!
THE DEMON KING'S DAUGHTER IS TRYING
TO CHANGE HER IMAGE TOO MUCH!!
"The Demon King's Daughter Is Trying
to Change Her Image Too Much!!"
Look, look!
My bedhead's all weird!
Lady Doux, what are you doing?
No! His Majesty's daughter mustn't
walk around with her hair like that!
Now, now, it's quite all right, Jahi.
It's not like she's doing
anything nice or anything.
Isn't that right, Doux?
Papa!
Again!
That's what I mean when I
say you're not demon-like!
Ow...
Big Sister?
A-Again...
It's not just kindness. It's how you
speak and look, as well!
If she's going to become a full-fledged
demon, we need to fix these things, too!
Hm...
You're indeed correct. But...
Would you wipe that
grin off of your face?!
But it's going to take a while to
adjust the way she speaks, won't it?
We've had no luck with that so far.
Then let's start by
changing her appearance.
Her appearance?
We will have Lady Doux undergo
a transformation trial.
First I'm gonna draw this roundy round...
And then these pointy points...
All done!
Very good. You should be able to
activate the spell using this.
I can transform with this?
We're still preparing.
In order to transform,
you'll need to enter the magic circle
while imagining the form you
want to transform into,
then say the incantation.
Lady Doux, do you see that over there?
Oh, it's the old guys!
They are repairing the areas that
were broken during training.
And now, Lady Doux...
Hey!
Lady Doux, you will
transform into a monster,
attack those slaves, and
rule over them with fear!
That is your trial this time!
What kind of monster?
Allow me to show you.
Variant!
Wow...
You look super strong!
Yes.
You transform to make yourself
look stronger and terrifying
and to hide your weakness.
Hide your weakness?
Now, Lady Doux, give it a try.
Okay!
Hm...
A monster, a monster...
The same kinda monster as Big Sister.
She should be able to imagine this
now that I've shown her an example.
I'll make sure she transforms properly
and make today's trial a success!
Variant!
Heh, I got a tail.
Don't, "I got a tail," me!
Did you actually imagine
your form properly?!
You need to look harder!
Like these fangs!
And these wings!
These giant ears!
That's bedhead!
These horns...
Horns?
Hmm... This might be a little hard.
It's no use.
She's turning more and more
into some mascot character.
But why?
Lady Doux should have
more than enough mana...
So why...
I did it!
I've got three horns!
Big Sister Jahi?
It looks like...
I'm going to have to use
the ace up my sleeve.
What's that?
This is the Flower of Transfiguration
that His Majesty gave
me before this trial.
It's a flower that only blooms
once every twenty years.
Just by covering yourself with its pollen,
you can transform into a giant monster.
Use it in an emergency.
This flower is rare, so I was hoping
you'd be able to transform on your own...
but you leave me no choice.
Now, Lady Doux, this time you
will successfully transform...
and show the humans just... how
t-terrifying demons can be...?
I'm a monster!
No, you just got bigger!
D-Doux?
Wow, why'd she get so big?
Everyone! I'm a big monster now!
Rawr!
"DOUX'S MARCH"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: TAKERU TAKEMIYA
SONG: DOUX
Ah, Lady Doux! Where are you going?!
There Doux goes on her march
Lookee, Lookee, I turned all big
Just look at how big I got
Every little thing is just so small
Papa and Big Sister are also small
Everyone's so cute and small
I'll let you all ride on my back
There Doux goes on her march
Lookee, Lookee, I turned all big
Just look at how big I got
Every little thing is just so small
Even Ms. Salamandra is so small
The castle's all tiny, too
Now I can't get into my room
The fact that her body's gotten bigger
must also mean that she's gotten stronger!
Lady Doux! Pulverize those slaves!
Doux's heading this way.
She's so cute even at that size.
Hey!
Get away from the cliff!
A boulder's about to fall!
Huh?
Lady Doux!
Doux!
W-We're saved...
It's all thanks to you, Lady Doux...
Doux, are you all right?
L-L-L-Lady Doux?!
Are you hurt?
We're fine thanks to you, Doux.
More importantly, are
you okay, Lady Doux?!
Yup! Doux is really strong!
Okay, bye!
Lady Doux!
I can't believe you
saved the humans again.
I haven't been able to teach
Lady Doux a single thing...
I guess I don't deserve to be
their attendant after all...
Lady Doux?
L-Lady Doux?!
I-It's okay!
It doesn't hurt! It doesn't hurt at all!
I didn't... cry in front of everyone.
Huh?
Because... I transformed.
Transformed...
You transform to make yourself
look stronger and terrifying
and to hide your weakness.
Hide your weakness?
I see... So she was listening to me.
Yes. You did very well hiding your pain.
Big Sister?
You're very strong, Lady Doux.
So a bump like this is nothing.
Yup! It's nothing!
I'm fine, too.
Thank you very much, Lady Doux.
Doux?!
How'd you get that bump on your head?!
What in the world happened, Doux?!
XXX IS TOO PERFECT A JOB FOR A PAIRIKA!!
"XXX Is Too Perfect a Job for a Pairika!!"
WE DELIVER EVERYWHERE: DEMON WORLD DELIVERY DRIVERS
HIGH PAY!! LOOKING FOR DRIVERS
"High pay!"
"We deliver everywhere: Demon
World Delivery Drivers."
But I don't have my license...
"Work anytime twenty-four hours!"
"Demon World Convenience Store
clerk. Training time included."
That sounds like a pain.
LOOKING FOR MONSTER BREEDERS
EXPERIENCE NEEDED
"Experience needed"?
Everyone has to start off somewhere!
All of these suck.
There has to be one somewhere,
right? A job just for me.
Master!
Hey, hey. Show me a new prank.
Doux...
So you've finally come, Jahi.
Now, fight the great Thaiti!
We'll compete over the position
of royal attendant!
Okay, Lady Doux, let's
go head to your trial.
Don't you ignore me! You meatheaded woman!
Don't come at me, you oaf!
What are you even talking about?!
Also, what happened to your Pairika job?
I quit.
Huh?
You remember that trial of
seduction we did, right?
Go back home and
suck on your mommy's teats.
I'll murder you!
That's when I realized that I'm
just not suited for seduction.
Big Sister Jahi.
Watch this!
It's a huge success!
I made this with Master.
Right?
Ever since then, Doux's acknowledged
me as her master in pranks, and
we've been playing together.
That's when it hit me...
that I should actually
be Doux's attendant.
Yes, I absolutely should be!
This little...
That's why we're going to fight!
I'll prove that I'm better
as her attendant!
Hey, look. I made this with Master, too.
Sit, sit!
Yay!
Master's pranks are the best! The best!
All right. I accept!
That's the spirit!
But only if the condition is whoever
loses won't meet with Lady Doux again.
Oh? Are you really okay with
adding a condition like that?
Yes.
Because there's absolutely no
chance that you'll defeat me.
Let's go!
Huh?
Hup, hup. Hup, hup.
Hup, hup, hup.
Hup, hup, huppity, hup!
Hup!
Wow, that's amazing!
You've made such a mess so
quickly just by using magic.
Thank you for your
assistance, Your Majesty.
Oh, it was nothing.
This is for your battle, after all.
Yeah! Battle!
W-W-Wait. Is this battle...
That's right!
We're going to compete by
doing household chores!
Wha?! Why would we do chores?!
What?
I mean, weak little me
wouldn't stand a chance in some
battle of magic or strength.
Not to mention a real lady like me can't
stand the sight of blood and guts.
This is going to be fair and smart.
That's how we'll do things.
You're gonna fairly smash each
other like sumo wrestlers?
DOSUKOI!
I said fair and smart!
Whatever. Fine.
Okay! First, we're going to clean!
You do the right half and
I'll do the left half.
Whoever cleans everything quicker wins!
You fool.
I already know that
you leave basically all the
cleaning to your housekeeper.
This battle is mine!
Hm... I feel like Thaiti's side is
messier than when we started somehow.
So you really are an oaf.
Here's a hanky.
No! This was just an accident!
Also, why does my side have
a chimney?! That's not fair!
You picked the sides, remember?
A-Anyway, this round doesn't count!
It doesn't!
Fine. I guess I'll have to go through
with this until she's satisfied.
Next! Onto the next!
LAUNDRY BATTLE
Laundry battle!
JAHI
THAITI
Next!
SEWING BATTLE
Sewing battle!
JAHI
THAITI
Next!
DIY BATTLE
DIY battle!
Why can you do all this
stuff, you dumb meathead?!
Who are you calling "meathead"?
Chores don't phase me.
This is nothing compared to what
I endured during magic training.
You should just give up already.
No!
I'm going to be the one
to take care of Doux!
GURGLE...
I'm hungry.
Next is a cooking battle!
Om...
Yummy!
Ah, this is delicious.
Well done, Thaiti!
I know, right? It is, isn't it?
Oh, there's plenty more, too.
I see. Isn't that wonderful, Doux?
Yeah!
I see. I guess I can cook.
Come to think of it, I did
help Mom cook pretty often.
I totally forgot.
Hm?
What... is this?
W-Well, I may have burnt it a little...
but what's important is the taste!
You're right.
Let's have a taste...
Your Majesty!
What the heck, Jahi?! What
did you even put in that?!
Er, um... This shouldn't have
happened... Lady Doux?!
She's not even touching it.
Well, this is a surprise. I had
no idea you can't cook, Jahi.
Okay, Doux.
I want you to decide on your attendant
judging from this cooking battle.
Wait!
Doux gets to decide?
Well, I don't think His Majesty
can make any decisions right now.
Hm...
No...
And I finally felt like I was doing
okay as her attendant the other day...
And yet...
And I'll lose my position as attendant
because of some cooking?
Okay!
I win!
What's an attendant?
What?!
Oh, I know what an atranatrana is, though!
You hit those like a xylophone!
ATTENDANT
We're talking about an
attendant! An attendant!
The one who's always by your side
and takes care of you and
teaches you a bunch of things.
Oh!
Hm... But...
There's training... and pranks...
Doux likes both!
I want both of my big
sisters to teach me those.
So I don't want either
of you to go away...
Never ever!
Doux...
Lady Doux...
Om!
Lady Doux! You don't need to
force yourself to eat that!
Yeah! You saw how much
His Majesty suffered!
Yum.
Huh?
I love sweet potatoes.
It tastes like potatoes and sugar.
This was supposed to be
a sweet potato dessert?
Lady Doux's favorite foods...
Sweet potatoes... and dark matter.
I guess she did mention it's sweet before.
Big Sister Jahi!
You remembered my favorite foods!
N-No, this was just a coincidence...
Seconds, please!
Of course!
Looks like the competition was a tie.
I won't accept this.
I'm going to keep challenging
you until I win!
Or so she said as she ran off, but
she hasn't made a peep since.
What in the world is she
up to, I wonder.
Ah! What's this?
I don't remember this cafeteria
being so popular before...
What is this? It's super tasty!
I've never eaten anything
like this before.
You can't be serious! Who
made this delicious food?
You've got some skills, missy.
Thaiti was scouted by the
cook at the demon castle's cafeteria.
I've finally found the perfect job for me!